[
    {
        "question": "The sun",
        "choice1": "el sol",
        "choice2": "las nubes",
        "choice3": "la llovizna",
        "choice4": "el calor",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The clouds",
        "choice1": "el tornado",
        "choice2": "las nubes",
        "choice3": "la lluvia",
        "choice4": "el calor",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The fog",
        "choice1": "el pronóstico",
        "choice2": "el calor",
        "choice3": "la niebla",
        "choice4": "el sol",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The mist",
        "choice1": "la lluvia",
        "choice2": "el tornado",
        "choice3": "la llovizna",
        "choice4": "la neblina",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "The rain",
        "choice1": "la lluvia",
        "choice2": "el granizo",
        "choice3": "la neblina",
        "choice4": "el calor",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The drizzle",
        "choice1": "el pronóstico",
        "choice2": "la llovizna",
        "choice3": "la lluvia",
        "choice4": "el granizo",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The storm",
        "choice1": "el granizo",
        "choice2": "el pronóstico",
        "choice3": "la tormenta",
        "choice4": "la lluvia",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The tornado",
        "choice1": "las nubes",
        "choice2": "el pronóstico",
        "choice3": "el granizo",
        "choice4": "el tornado",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "The thunder",
        "choice1": "el trueno",
        "choice2": "el relámpago",
        "choice3": "el sol",
        "choice4": "el tornado",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The lightening strike",
        "choice1": "la neblina",
        "choice2": "el relámpago",
        "choice3": "el rayo",
        "choice4": "la temperatura",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The lightening bolt",
        "choice1": "la llovizna",
        "choice2": "el frío",
        "choice3": "el rayo",
        "choice4": "el relámpago",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The wind",
        "choice1": "el sol",
        "choice2": "el frío",
        "choice3": "el relámpago",
        "choice4": "el viento",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "The breeze",
        "choice1": "la brisa",
        "choice2": "las nubes",
        "choice3": "el relámpago",
        "choice4": "el frío",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The hail",
        "choice1": "el trueno",
        "choice2": "el granizo",
        "choice3": "la brisa",
        "choice4": "la niebla",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The ice",
        "choice1": "la niebla",
        "choice2": "la brisa",
        "choice3": "el hielo",
        "choice4": "el trueno",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The snow",
        "choice1": "el trueno",
        "choice2": "la niebla",
        "choice3": "la brisa",
        "choice4": "la nieve",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "The heat",
        "choice1": "el calor",
        "choice2": "la brisa",
        "choice3": "la neblina",
        "choice4": "la tormenta",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The cold",
        "choice1": "el rayo",
        "choice2": "el frío",
        "choice3": "la tormenta",
        "choice4": "el sol",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The humidity",
        "choice1": "la tormenta",
        "choice2": "el trueno",
        "choice3": "la humedad",
        "choice4": "las nubes",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "The temperature",
        "choice1": "la niebla",
        "choice2": "la tormenta",
        "choice3": "el rayo",
        "choice4": "la temperatura",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "The forecast",
        "choice1": "el pronóstico",
        "choice2": "la llovizna",
        "choice3": "la neblina",
        "choice4": "el frío",
        "answer": 1
    }
]